Hey, man, I think it's about
time we haul it up out of here.
Yeah, might be.
Let me finish this first.
It's a nice night, though.
It's quiet.
A little too quiet.
This place always gave me
the heebie-jeebies, man.
This water's so murky.
It's shit water.
I almost drowned in it once
when I was like eight.
Actually, right over there
by the beach.
My cousin had to drag me out.
I don't know what it was, man.
I just felt like
I was being pulled.
You probably was.
By what?
There's a whole town
underneath us.
The hell out of here, man.
That's what I'm saying.
Shit water.
This whole lake
used to be a town.
Houses, barns, roads.
There's a whole raceway
down there.
State government built a dam
and flooded the place.
Anyone who didn't leave drowned.
Town was Black, too.
What?
Self-governed Black town.
So, there are Black people
under us right now?
Yeah. Why you think
so many people die
around here every year?
'Cause of drunk rednecks
trying to fish at night.
Like you.
No.
It's 'cause it's haunted.
You-you really think
it's haunted?
Oh, yeah.
Lot of souls down there.
That's what pulled you under.
Town full of Black folk.
They were almost white.
Get the hell out of here, man.
What are you talking about?
They were almost white?
White's not a real thing, right?
There's no scientific basis
for it.
People just... become white.
It's social.
White is where you are.
It's when you are.
Armenians are white as hell
till they ain't.
Armenians?
When they dammed
the Chattahoochee,
some refused to leave.
They thought they were safe.
They'd paid to be white.
With enough blood and money,
anyone can be white.
It's always been that way.
But the thing about
being white is
it blinds you.
It's easy to see
the Black man as cursed
because you've separated
yourself from him.
But you don't know...
you're enslaved just like him.
Cold whiteness.
You're hypothermic.
You lose logic.
You see the blood...
...and you think
someone else is bleeding.
Everyone is screaming at you
to turn the machine off,
but you can't hear them.
You can't even
hear yourself saying,
- "We're cursed, too."
We're cursed, too!
Oh, shit!
I don't want to keep
reminding you about this.
- Oh, and one more thing
before we go.
- Listen up, everyone.
I have a special announcement
to make.
In an effort
to promote more Black history
in the curriculum,
our school has partnered up
with the Atlanta Falcons
and Domino's Pizza
for the
Change Atlanta Initiative.
So, next Thursday,
we're all going on a field trip.
We're all going
to go watch a movie.
The new Black Panther 2.
- Let's go!
- I know. Okay.
I know. It's exciting...
- Oh.
- Loquareeous.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
- Loquareeous, sit down!
- Hey! Hey!
- Loquareeous!
Loquareeous, sit down right now!
Hey! Hey!
Loquareeous, sit down right now,
young man!
Hi, Mom.
Please. Come in and have a seat.
Mm-hmm.
How's everyone doing today?
First of all,
I done already told y'all
to stop calling me down here.
Well, I really appreciate you
coming down, Ms. Reid.
And you're Loquareeous's
grandfather, right?
Thank you both for coming.
As you know,
there was a disruption
- with Loquareeous...
- Uh, let me jump in here.
Sorry. Uh, I'm the guidance
counselor, Mrs. Grier.
Let me start by saying
I am a big fan of your son.
He's been
to my office a few times
already this semester
for disciplinary problems--
talking in class,
being disruptive...
- Well, then give him detention.
- Well, yes.
He's-he's had detention before.
Several times.
But I-I had a thought.
Maybe the reason that he's being
disruptive in class
is because the material
is too challenging.
If we put him in remedial math
and language arts,
he could have the...
Wait. Wait.
What? No.
- My son is not dumb.
- Oh, no, no.
He's an idiot.
Y'all ridiculous.
He is not the first kid
to act up in class,
and you want to push him back
some grades?
No, I just thought
it could be...
Don't you move my son.
Tell his teachers
to give him detention.
- Thank you for coming.
- Mm-hmm.
Okay, that went very well.
I thought I... I-I think
he could really use the...
Ms. Reid?
- I'm sorry.
Uh-uh! You better dance!
Since you love to dance so much,
go 'head.
Shoot it. Come on, shoot!
You got these people up here
thinking you retarded.
Your ass gonna end up
in them SPED classes.
Now whip.
Mm-hmm.
Nae Nae. Come on.
Ay. Ay. Ay.
Hit it. Hit it!
If you don't start using your
common sense and acting right,
these white people--
they gon' kill you.
- Ms. Reid, d...
- Kill... you.
- Now do the worm.
- Really,
there's no need for that.
- Let's see it.
- There's no need for that.
You up here showing out
for your white classmates.
Yeah,
you laughing with them now,
but they're gonna be
the only ones laughing
when you dead or in jail.
I wasn't even trying
to show out...
I don't want to hear it!
- What's your problem?
- Now get to class.
And I better not get
another call from this school.
I'll walk him back.
Don't worry.
I'm gonna get you out of there.
Mom, there ain't no more milk!
There's spaghetti in
the refrigerator if you hungry.
You better not be
watching that TV.
I'm-a check, and I'll know.
Hello. Ms. Reid, right?
Who wants to know?
I'm with Family
and Children's Services.
I'm here on behalf of the city
to conduct a welfare ch...
- Family and Children's Services?
- Yes, ma'am.
I'm here to conduct
a welfare check on your son...
- Loqua...
- Loquareeous!
- Oh, yes.
- Uh-huh.
- Get in here!
- See, y'all got me fucked up.
- Oh, ma'am, I just need a few
- moments to speak with you.
- Did you call the police on me?
- No.
- Oh, Ms. Reid,
the police are just here
as a precaution.
Take him.
Go ahead.
- Ma.
- Since you want
to go so bad, bye.
Ma, I didn't call nobody.
- You know what?
- Wait.
Mom.
Mama, I didn't call nobody.
I ain't giving you
all these clothes that I bought.
Y'all better take this boy
- Before I kill him...
- Mom.
- ...and he got a real reason
to call the police.
Mom.
Mama, wait!
Oh, my goodness.
Welcome home, son. Okay.
Quickly, get inside.
Thank you so much
for doing this last minute.
We always appreciate it, Amber.
Oh, it's not a problem at all.
It's what we do.
All right, well,
let's get you settled.
I am Amber,
but you can call me "Mom."
Um, oh, those are
your new brothers and sisters.
That's Lanre, Yves and Fatima.
Ugh. It's stinky here.
Oh, no, no, no,
it doesn't stink.
Come on, this way.
We've kind of turned our kitchen
into a workshop.
We're trying to make
an olive oil shampoo,
and we started mixing together
some African Dudu soap.
It's not what it sounds like.
We make our own kombucha.
Yummy, huh?
And we pickle our own veggies
using our organic garden.
Um, we're selling it
at the farmers market tomorrow.
You're gonna love it.
Oh, um, and that is
your other mom.
And that little guy is Cornpop.
Welcome to the family.
So do I call you both "Mom"?
- Yes.
- Call me Gayle.
Oh, dinner's at 5:30,
so wash up first.
Um, we're having fried chicken.
And, um, since it's your first
night, I'll let you decide.
Do you want capers or sprouts?
I don't know what that is.
- Aw.
Capers it is.
- Oh, will you get me
that chicken over there?
- Mm. Mm.
Perfect.
Uh, how much
did we do it last time?
- 12 minutes is too long, right?
- Yeah.
- It was a little dry.
- Okay, let's do
eight and a half, then.
Mm-hmm.
Hey.
I just wanted to see
that you were settled in.
I made you something special
for your first day.
This says "Larry."
Oh, well, I didn't know
how to spell "Loo-Kway-reeous,"
so I figured
we'd call you "Larry."
Larry's a great nickname. Hmm.
Um, where's the washcloth?
It's okay. He's new here.
You just use your hands.
Even on my butt?
Oh, we need to take a picture.
Get around.
Get the towel.
- Okay.
Perfect!
What are you wearing?
Pajamas.
You can wear that tonight,
but from now,
I'll lay your clothes out.
You can sprinkle
some rosemary on it if you want.
Mm-mm. Mmm. It's great.
Mmm.
Larry, you're not eating.
This food is nasty.
If I eat it, I'll throw up.
Larry, we do not say
"throw up" at the table.
But it's nasty.
No, honey.
It's just better for you.
There's too much salt and oil
in most of the foods
that you're used to.
Oh, did you see
on Instagram today
that Rihanna used the phrase
"spirit animal"?
No. Please.
Please tell me that Rihanna
is an indigenous person
- and I just don't know it.
- Uh-uh.
Oh, my God. We got to comment
on that, right?
Mm.
Hello.
This is she.
We're having dinner.
I don't understand
why the bill collectors
are always
just calling during dinner.
- I put us on that
"do not call" list.
- Well, they're calling.
This food is nasty!
Larry, we don't...
You want to know something?
There are starving children
in Africa.
You don't believe me,
ask your brother.
I want a hamburger.
- We don't have hamburgers.
That's what the dog is eating.
- Well, yeah,
that's Cornpop's food.
You don't..? Okay, you don't
want to eat, you can go to bed.
- It's 6:00!
- Okay.
- Man, I hate this house!
We don't use the word
"hate" in this house.
Hate, hate, hate, hate,
hate, hate, hate, hate!
So, this is the last
that Marcos can give us
on credit.
Hey. We're gonna have to make
some more adjustments.
We didn't eat lunch.
You had celery and carrots,
remember?
I'm still hungry.
You're supposed to be hungry.
If you're full,
that means you ate too much.
How much longer
do we have to do this?
Why don't you try
singing a song while you work?
It might make you feel better.
Sing something silly,
like, um...
Okay, back to work, Larry.
We got to leave for the
farmers market in 30 minutes.
Oh, your family's so cute.
Oh, thank you so much.
Larry,
can you put some effort in?
Shake your booty. Come on.
Aw. Is Hugs your father?
No.
- Larry.
- Whoa. Oh.
- Whoa! Kid, I almost shot you!
- I learned my lesson.
I hate my new parents.
They can't cook,
- and they make me sleep
in a storage closet.
- All right.
Slow down.
Y... Your parents did this?
My moms.
They make me do all the chores,
and I didn't eat nothing.
Please take me home.
- I'm tired
of these white ladies.
- All right, calm down.
- I don't know
what you're talking...
- Excuse me, Officer.
Is there a problem?
Um, that's our son.
- This is your son?
- Yes.
Yeah. My wife, Amber and I--
we adopt impoverished children.
We have a kombucha stand
right over there.
Did you want some?
Oh. I see what's going on.
Okay. I think
he's just tired is all.
He said he wanted to go home.
Maybe he thought I'd arrest you
for not letting him
play PlayStation.
- Uh, well,
all four of our children
are Black, so we always
make sure to tell them that
the police are their friends.
Yeah.
- Come on.
- Hey.
You know who he reminds me of
in that hat?
Aloe Blacc.
- Yes. Exactly.
- Yeah.
- Thank you so much.
- Come on.
Larry, you are helping so much.
I'm so proud of you.
I didn't say that shit!
I know being here
isn't easy for you...
...but I am gonna love that
right out of you.
I promise.
You know, where you come from,
they have a name
for what you are.
What?
A snitch.
We all have to work hard
to keep this family together.
And I'm sure this is
a much better situation
than where you came from.
Goddamn it.
May I help you?
Hi. I'm with
Family and Children's Services.
We got a call
from one of your neighbors
and would like to do
a wellness check on the kids.
Mm-hmm.
- May I come in?
- Mm.
Look, if it was
Chris Meyers next door,
I mean, you can't really believe
anything that he says.
- He's, like, one of those
Bernie Bro women-haters.
- Excuse me.
What is that smell?
Uh, kombucha.
Pickled brussels sprouts.
Both.
So, I was going over your file,
and I noticed
- that you moved here
five months ago.
- Mm-hmm.
But when I called
Bledsoe County,
they said that they could not
locate a record.
Well, normally,
Kasey's our caseworker.
Did something happen?
She's sick.
There is dog hair
- everywhere in here.
Hello, darling.
Are you feeling okay?
Oh.
What is this?
Blueberries, like medicine.
Okay. Do you have
a washcloth I can use?
Uh, no.
So how do you like living here?
I'm really, really hungry.
I just want to go home.
Don't worry.
I'm gonna get you out of here.
Um, you know, could I speak
with you privately?
I just think that there's
some things about our case
you don't... you don't know.
- Um, sure. That's fine.
- We'll go here.
Amber, why don't you
start dinner.
Larry's hungry.
Everything's fine.
- We're good.
- Well, that's fantastic.
I made fried chicken again.
Eat up, guys.
If you don't start using
your common sense
and acting right,
these white people--
they gon' kill you.
Kill you!
What's your problem?
Amber?
Oh. Hey, Larry.
Oh, we're going
to the Grand Canyon.
You should get dressed.
Grand Canyon?
Yeah. It's gonna be fun.
Where are we going? Really.
Larry, get dressed.
We got to get going
before the sun goes down.
Okay. Let's go, guys.
Larry?
Come on. Let's go.
Okay, Cornpop.
Go be free.
Go.
Hey, Cornpop's a survivor, okay?
He's-he's gonna make it.
Someone's gonna
take care of him.
What the hell are we doing?
Well, we're doing
what needs to be done.
You know the world
we live in, Amber.
It's horrible for these kids.
Without us to protect them,
what's gonna happen to them?
They're gonna go back
into foster care.
Just release them in the wild
like Cornpop?
We'd be prolonging
the inevitable.
Uh, when we adopted Fatima,
I knew we were doing
the right thing.
The agency even said so.
I mean, we got that big loan
from the bank.
I thought that... I thought
that meant we were solid.
Everyone was so supportive.
Every single person.
And I just kept thinking,
"Why...
Why isn't anyone stopping us?"
Why didn't anyone stop us,
Gayle?
I... I don't think
I can do this.
Don't look back.
Larry!
So you finally decided
to come home, huh?
Wait, Mom.
Yeah, baby?
Some spaghetti in there?
Yeah, spaghetti in there.
Shocking news tonight.
Authorities found children
at a rest stop,
apparently abandoned
after their adoptive parents
committed suicide
by driving off of a bridge...
Terrible story.